(Penny:)Okay, just for the record,
I have never entered a wet T-shirt contest.
(Penny:)I've won a few, but that's just
because I spill when I'm drunk.
(Amy:)We could go to the cadaver lab at UCLA
and play real-life Operation.
(Sheldon:)- No.
- Uh-uh.
(Penny:)I don't think so.
(Amy:)You sure?
The nose doesn't light up...
(Amy:)...but if the corpse is fresh enough
sometimes you can get the leg to jerk.
(Howard:)Hey, Ma, twinkle, twinkle,
your little star is home!
Ma, the chain's on the door!
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)Howard? I thought
I wasn't going to see you till tomorrow!
(Howard:)Yeah, well, Bernie's not feeling well,
so I thought I'd stop by.
(Howard:)Tell you about
the greatest adventure of my life.
(Howard:)See if you can make me feel bad about it.
Okay! Hold on, I'm not decent!
(Leonard:)All right.